humaxdigital.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | HUMAX-United Kingdom

We will treat all your personal information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable rules and laws in effect. 

When you use this website, we will ask you to input and will collect certain personal information from you such as your name and e-mail address (“Personal Information”). We may also collect, and our third party providers of advertisements and contents may collect, information about where you are on the internet (e.g. the URL you came from, IP address, domain types), your browser type, the area where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our website (“User Information”). We may collect this User Information even if you do not register with us. 

You should be aware that this website is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service, or be used to present you with Humax products which are relevant to your browsing history when you visit other websites. 

We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the applicable rules and laws in effect. 

We use your information only for the following purposes:  
– For statistical or survey purposes to improve this website and its services to you;  
– To serve website content and advertisements to you;  
– To administer this website;  
– If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. 

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes by e-mail or otherwise (if other information is provided by you). When you create an account at this website, you will be given the option to receive information from Humax by e-mail or otherwise about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. 

In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, ensure that you tick the appropriate box as you go through the registration process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by replying to a promotional e-mail with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line, by e-mailing us at uksupport@humax-digital.co.uk or telephoning us on 0344 318 8800 from Monday to Friday between 9am and 5.30pm. 

You hereby agree that your Personal Information may be disclosed to other business entity within the group companies of Humax and to reputable third parties that conduct a business with Humax. Humax requires all such third parties to treat your Personal Information as fully confidential and to fully comply with all applicable rules and laws in effect. We will not release your Personal Information to any company outside of Humax for mailing or marketing purposes. You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information, we are entitled do so. 

Humax will take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access. The ways of securing such Personal Information include:  
-Limiting physical access to our premises;  
-Limiting access to the information we collect about you;  
-Requiring any third party providers to have acceptable security measures to keep Personal Information secure; and  
-Putting in place physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in line with industry standards.

If Humax no longer requires your Personal Information and are not legally required to retain, Humax will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify the Personal Information.

When entering any of our contests or prize draws, you may be asked to provide your name, email address and postal address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contest or prize draw, you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the website. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received. 

### What are cookies?

Cookies are tiny text files stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. At this website, we use cookies to keep track of what you have viewed, and to remember you when you return to our site. If you don’t wish to enable cookies, you can disable cookies and you will still be able to browse the site and use it for research purposes. Most web browsers have cookies enabled, but please see internet browser’s help menu to turn them on/off should you need to. Please note that cookies can’t harm your computer. We don’t store personally identifiable information in cookies we create, but we do use encrypted information gathered from them to help improve your experience of the website. For example, they help us to identify and resolve errors, or to determine relevant related products to show you when you’re browsing. 

### Our cookies policy 

To make full use of this website, your computer, tablet or mobile phone may need to accept cookies, as we can only provide you with certain personalized features of this website by using them. Our cookies do not store sensitive information such as your name or email address. Instead, they simply hold the key that, once you’re signed in, is associated with this information. However, if you prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from this website, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone’s handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please bear in mind that if you disable certain cookies for this website, you’ll be unable to access certain types of content on the website, such as videos. 

### Sharing tools 

If you take the opportunity to share this website’s content with friends through social networks – such as Facebook and Twitter – you may be sent cookies from these websites. We do not control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them. 

### Further information about cookies 

If you desire to learn more about cookies in general and how to manage them, visit aboutcookies.org (opens in a new window). Please note that we are not responsible for the content of external websites. 

### General 

We may from time to time change, alter, adapt, add or remove portions of this privacy policy, but if we do so, we will post any changes on the website. If any provision of this policy is held by any competent authority to be invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part, the validity of the other provisions of these terms and conditions and the remainder of the provision in question will not be affected. The laws of UK will apply to this privacy policy. The headings in this privacy policy are for convenience only and will not affect their interpretation. 

Last updated Nov.20, 2016.
